cduniverse.com 2011-05-21

# CD Universe - Help

**What information is collected by CD Universe and how is this information used?**

We automatically collect and store the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access one of our sites; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to our site, address our users' preferences and to attract new users, and, in some instances, to properly credit third-parties who refer users to our site. 

In addition to the information we automatically collect any time a user visits our site, we also ask users to voluntarily provide certain information so that users can take full advantage of the services and features offered at our site. Users of our site are often able to enter contests and sign up to receive electronic newsletters. To provide these services to our users, we generally request that the user provide no more than a name and an email address. We do not require any of our users to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity as a condition of participation. We use the information collected to distribute the requested newsletter or other content, to notify contest winners, to enable password protected access to certain services and sections within our site, and to provide whatever other service the user has authorized in providing the contact information. 

To make a purchase at our site, users are asked to provide their name, email address, mailing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date. Once entered, this information is usually saved by the site. When you choose to make future purchases through our site, this information automatically appears in the appropriate spaces on the web page within the site for placing orders. 

**What Information does CD Universe store about my visit?**

CD Universe or any of its third party affiliates, may during the course of your visit to our site, store "cookies" on your computer. Cookies are small pieces of information that an internet website can put on your computer to help track information about your visit. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer by adjusting the preferences of your web browser. 

**Does CD Universe disclose this information to anyone?**

CD Universe does not sell, trade, lease or distribute the personal information of its registered users. However, if you accept an offer made by our third party marketing partners, we may with your permission pass your relevant personal information, including name, address or email address. Please note that CD Universe's privacy policy does not cover the web sites or web pages that link to the CD Universe Network of sites and services. 

We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, cookies or web beacons. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user. 

Some of these services can be opted out by clicking the links below:  
Channel Advisor: Opt Out  
Fetchback: Opt Out  
Google Adsense: [Opt Out](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)  
Advertising.com & AdBrite: [Opt Out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)  

**How does CD Universe protect this information?**

All transmissions of personal user information are through CD Universe's secure computer servers which run authentication and data encryption software. Access to registered users' accounts on our site is password protected. 

**How do we handle individually identifiable information collected from children under the age of 13 years old?**

In general, CD Universe is comprised of general interest/audience sites and is not directed at children under the age of 13\. It is CD Universe’s policy to refrain from knowingly collecting personally identifying information from children 12 or under and to actively discourage children from providing such information at points of collection. 

**How may I get more information about CD Universe's privacy policy?**

If you would like any additional information about CD Universe's privacy policy or have any questions or comments, please email us at [privacy@cduniverse.com](mailto:privacy@cduniverse.com).
